Git is not configured to allow long paths. This can cause issues with Shorebird's Flutter checkout. Please run 'git config --system core.longpaths true' to enable long paths.
Login as a new Shorebird user.

Usage: shorebird login [arguments]
-h, --help        Print this usage information.
-p, --provider    The authentication provider to use.
                  [google, microsoft]

Run "shorebird help" to see global options.
